[{"question": " okay, the reason why i asked you guys out to brunch today is because i have been doing some thinking about who should be my maid of honor.", "answer": " oh my god! this is it!   i really hope it&#146;s you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " i hope it&#146;s you.", "answer": " me too!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " first of all um, i love you both so much and you&#146;re both so important to me&#133;", "answer": " okay, bla-bla-bla-bla!! who is it?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " well umm, i was thinking that maybe we could come up with a system where we trade of being maid of honor for each other. like hypothetically, if phoebe were mine&#133;", "answer": " yes!!! oh!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " hypothetically!", "answer": " still.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " if phoebe were my maid of honor&#133;", "answer": " uh-hmm.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " rachel would be phoebe&#146;s, i would be rachel&#146;s, that way we all get to do it once and no one would get upset.", "answer": " yeah that&#146;s actually a pretty good idea.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " yeah, i&#146;ll do that. so who gets to be yours?", "answer": "  well that&#146;s the best part. umm, you guys get to decide!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " wh-why is that the best part?", "answer": " because then i don&#146;t have to!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " well of course we will help you decide! we will do anything we can to help you! now, i would like to make a toast, to the future mrs. chandler bing , my best friend, and truly one of the nicest people that&#133;", "answer": " i&#146;m really not deciding!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " excuse me, i-i couldn&#146;t help overhearing, you&#146;re marrying chandler bing?", "answer": " yeah that&#146;s right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": "  huh, good luck!", "answer": " aww, and good luck to you too!  what a nice lady!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " die hard still great!", "answer": " yep. hey, what do you say we make it a double feature?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " what&#146;d you rent?", "answer": " die hard 2.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": "  joey, this is die hard 1 again.", "answer": " oh, well we watch it a second time and its die hard 2!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " joey, we just saw it!", "answer": " and?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " and it&#146;ll be cool to see it again! yeah! joey and ross: die hard!!!!!!", "answer": " dude, you didn&#146;t say die hard. is everything okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " yeah, i just got uh, got plans.", "answer": " well, john mclane had plans!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " no, see the thing is i want to get out of here before joey gets all worked up and starts calling everybody bitch.", "answer": " what are you talking about? bitch.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " hey rachel?", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " umm, when i get married will you be my maid of honor?", "answer": " really?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " uh-hmm.", "answer": " oh my god phoebe! i mean i&#146;m just&#151;wait a minute. if i&#146;m your maid of honor that means you are monica&#146;s.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " oh! well, if that&#146;s what you want&#133;", "answer": " ohh! no way phoebe! i want to be monica&#146;s!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " but why does it even matter?!", "answer": " why does it matter so much to you?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " because this one is now! and-and it&#146;s two of our best friends! who knows what you&#146;re gonna marry!", "answer": " what-what if i marry ross&#151;or joey?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": "  you wouldn&#146;t! okay look, rachel i know you really want to do this, but i-i&#146;ve never been maid of honor to anyone before! and i know you&#146;ve done it at least twice!", "answer": " yeah but phoebe&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " and no, oh please, oh please let me finish.  oh i guess that was it.", "answer": " okay. okay. it&#146;s&#151;since you&#146;ve never done it before you can be monica&#146;s made of honor.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " oh, thank you so much!  okay.", "answer": " i&#146;m gonna marry someone good y&#146;know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " oh i know.", "answer": " better than chandler.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " what happened?!!", "answer": " well, i don&#146;t know!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " we fell asleep! that is all.", "answer": " yeah. yep. yeah. all right, well uh, i&#146;d better go.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " i think that would be best.", "answer": " yeah. all right, i&#146;ll talk to you later.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " okay. but not about this!", "answer": " no! never! never!  bye.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " yeah hey, a weird thing happened today whey i was at brunch. this woman overheard that i was marrying you and-and then she&#133;she wished me good luck.", "answer": " that&#146;s sweet.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " no, it&#146;s more like a  good luck.", "answer": " so uh, what did this woman look like?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " she was like 30, dark hair, attractive.", "answer": " well, is there any chance you were looking into a bright, shiny thing called a mirror?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " come on, was it somebody maybe you dated in college?", "answer": " no, no i only dated two girls in college, both blonde, both not attractive&#133;  hold on one second; let me check this out. (he gets up and grabs a photo album.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " what are you doing?", "answer": " well, let&#146;s see&#133;  okay uh, is that her?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " oh my god yes! who is she?", "answer": " julie grath, my camp girlfriend.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " did you break up with her?", "answer": "  no, we&#146;re still together. yeah we went out for two summers, and then i broke up with her.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " why?", "answer": " well, &#145;cause she came back the third summer and she&#146;d gotten really fa-aa-aw-ow&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " fat?!", "answer": " i did not say fat! i said, &quot;fa-aa-aw-ow&#133;&quot;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " you broke up with a girl because she was fat?!", "answer": " yeah. yeah, but it was a really, really long time ago! does she still feel bad?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " well, apparently she does.", "answer": " well, you know what they say, elephants never forget.  seriously, good luck marrying me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " hey! what&#146;s going on?", "answer": " phoebe is gonna be monica&#146;s maid of honor!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": "  you have been maid of honor before?!!", "answer": " see? this is exactly why you shouldn&#146;t lie!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " all right that&#146;s it! i am maid of honor!", "answer": " na-uh, i am!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " how come you are?!", "answer": " because i cared enough to lie!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " hey-hey-hey-hey, i can help you decide who should do it! yeah, we could have like uh, like an audition and see how you&#146;d handle maid of honor type situations.", "answer": " what are you talking about?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " like when i want a job, i go to an audition and if i&#146;m the best of the people they see, they give me the part.", "answer": " okay, so after this audition, who decides who gets it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " oh uh, me and ross can be the judges.", "answer": "  well, it&#146;s better than us deciding.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " oh, come on! this is crazy! can&#146;t we just flip a coin?!", "answer": " no! coins hate me!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " okay. okay fine, y&#146;know what? we will let ross and joey decide.   hiiiii, ross! sweetie.", "answer": " hey there, you handsome thing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " wow, this cologne really is every bit as good as georgio.", "answer": " hi.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " just uh, brought back your videos.", "answer": " uh hey look uh ross, look i think we need to talk about before.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " no! no we don&#146;t!", "answer": " yes we do! now look, that was the best nap i ever had!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " i&#133; i don&#146;t know what you are talking about.", "answer": " come on! admit it! that was the best nap you ever had!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " i&#146;ve had better.", "answer": " okay! when?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " all right! all right! it was the best nap ever!", "answer": " uh-huh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " i&#146;ve said it! okay?! but it&#146;s over joey!", "answer": " i want to do it again.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " we can&#146;t do it again.", "answer": " why not?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " because it&#146;s weird!", "answer": " fine! do you want something to drink?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " sure, what do you got?", "answer": " warm milk and excedrin p.m.  commercial break", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " chandler!  chandler! i just figured out who you are!", "answer": " can you figure out what i&#146;m doing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " you&#146;re lewis posin.", "answer": " who?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " lewis posin! he was my best friend in fifth grade, and-and then one day i asked him to be my boyfriend and he said no. do you know why?", "answer": " because you kept talking to him while he was trying to go to the bathroom?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " no! but because he thought i was to faaaaa&#133;.  and every time i think about it, it makes me feel as bad as i did in fifth grade! y&#146;know, i-i really think that you should apologize to julie.", "answer": " what? are you kidding? that was like 16 years ago.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " no, i know. but y&#146;know what? it would make me feel better if lewis apologized to me.", "answer": " okay, i will do it. but i have to warn you; this may make me a better person and that is not the man you feel in love with!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " okay, all right, this is how it&#146;s going to work. we&#146;re gonna give you hypothetical maid of honor situations and you will be scored on a scale of 1 to 10, 1 being the highest.", "answer": " no, 10 is the highest.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " why is 10 the highest?", "answer": " because it&#146;s the highest.  okay, rachel you&#146;re up first.  situation no. 1: you&#146;re with monica, the wedding is about to start when monica gets cold feet. go!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": "  i don&#146;t want to marry chandler!", "answer": " okay, uh&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " i&#146;ve got cold feet.", "answer": " &#133;it&#146;s gonna be okay!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " no, one man for the rest of my life? i don&#146;t know if i can do it! this means i&#146;ll never get to sleep with joey!", "answer": " look monica, getting cold feet is very common. y&#146;know, it&#146;s-it&#146;s just because of all the anticipation and you just have to remember that you love chandler. and also, i ran out on a wedding. you don&#146;t get to keep the gifts.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": "  very good! drawing on your own experience, i like that!", "answer": " thanks!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " yes, very nice rachel.", "answer": " thank you judges.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " ugh, what a kiss ass.", "answer": " oh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " okay, phoebe&#133;", "answer": " yes! your honor?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " we&#146;re now in the ceremony, monica is about to say, &quot;i do&quot; when her drunk uncle starts yelling. what do you do? go!", "answer": "  when monica was a little girl, i remember that&#151;&#151;ooh!! ow! very good!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " oh!", "answer": " yes! excellent! perfect score!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " wait a minute! she just made a scene in the middle of the ceremony!", "answer": " hey! do you want do you want a little taste of pheebs?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " it is time for you to give your maid of honor speech.", "answer": " ohh, wait a minute, we haven&#146;t pre&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " go!", "answer": " okay! okay! umm, webster&#146;s dictionary defines marriage as&#133;  okay!! forget that! that sucks!! okay, never mind! forget it! umm, umm, okay, uh&#133; i met, i-i met, i met monica when we were just a couple of six year olds and i became friends with chandler when he was 25, although he seemed like a six year old. ross and joey: oh! that&#146;s nice.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " thank you. thank you very much. umm, i&#146;ve known them separately and i&#146;ve known them together and-and to know them as a couple is to know that you are truly in the presence of love. so i would like to raise my glass  to monica and chandler and the beautiful adventure they are about to embark upon together. i can think of no two people better prepared for the journey.", "answer": " wow.  good speech.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " yeah, it really was!", "answer": " aw, thanks!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " okay phoebe, i guess you&#146;re next  although i really don&#146;t see the point.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": "  julie hi! chandler bing, i, i guess you remember", "answer": " hello skidmark.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": "  it&#146;s a nickname, i&#146;ll explain later.", "answer": " it&#146;s pretty clear.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " ah, uh, i owe you a long overdue apology. i never should have broken up with you because you were overweight.", "answer": " that&#146;s why you broke up with me?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " all right, well first of all i would like to say that you both performed very well. okay? you should be proud of yourselves. and-and i would also like to say that in this competition there are no losers. well, except for rachel&#151;damnit!", "answer": " really?! i won!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " what?!", "answer": " i&#146;m sorry rach, it was, it was really close.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " actually, it wasn&#146;t that close.", "answer": " no! y&#146;know what? no! no! you thing was so stupid anyway, this was ridiculous&#151;we&#146;re gonna flip a coin!  all right?!  heads!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " the coins have finally forgiven me!", "answer": " well y&#146;know what? i hope monica forgives you after you throw her, her vegetarian, voodoo, goddess circley shower!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": "  rach, it&#146;s gonna be okay!  you guys are the best!", "answer": " boy i tell ya, that judging stuff took a lot out of me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " yeah?", "answer": " yeah! i was thinking about maybe going upstairs and taking a little nap on my couch.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " why-why would i care about that?", "answer": " no reason, i&#146;m just saying that uh&#133; that&#146;s where i&#146;ll be.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " as bad as that went i actually enjoyed myself. i think that i&#146;m going to apologize for all of the stupid things i do.", "answer": " why don&#146;t you just stop doing stupid things? then you wouldn&#146;t have to apologize.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " i would really love it if could do both.", "answer": " all right, i&#133;i have to ask.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " are you gonna break up with me if i get fat again?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " what?!", "answer": " well, you broke up with julie grath! how much weight could she have gained?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " a hundred and forty-five pounds.", "answer": " in one year?! my god what did she eat? her-her family! that&#146;s not the point.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " look i know it was a stupid reason to break up with somebody, but i was 15!", "answer": " well&#133; that&#146;s not the only time this was an issue. you remember when umm, you spent thanksgiving with us? you called me fat.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " okay. okay, now wait a minute that was totally different.", "answer": " how?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " you were not supposed to hear that! i said that behind you back!", "answer": " what if i have babies, okay? i mean i&#146;m gonna look different. i&#146;m okay with that, but i&#146;m not sure that you are!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " look you have to realize i don&#146;t think of you as a thin, beautiful woman.  see this is one of things that i can apologize for later! look, what i mean is you&#146;re monica! okay? and i am in love with monica.", "answer": " keep going.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " so you can balloon up or you can shrink down and i will still love you.", "answer": " even if i shrink down to two inches tall?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " i&#146;d carry you around in my pocket.", "answer": " i love you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " hi pheebs.", "answer": " hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " hi! i just want to apologize. i&#146;m really sorry i was a baby.", "answer": " that&#146;s ridiculous rachel, we were all babies once.  oh, you mean today.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " yeah. yeah, and y&#146;know you-you deserve to win. and-and y&#146;know i was thinking about it, if-if you&#146;re monica&#146;s maid of honor that means i get to be yours.", "answer": " oh yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " yeah! oh, umm when-when monica and chandler got engaged i started putting some stuff together, y&#146;know just in case&#133;", "answer": " oh that&#146;s so sweet thanks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " here is a book of poetry that i know monica loves. and-and ohh god this is funny, look, this is a picture of one halloween where she dressed up as a bride.  and look, she made me carry her train, which was weird because i was wonder woman. oh and here&#146;s a little purse that i found.  y&#146;know i just thought that maybe they could hold the rings in there.", "answer": " ohh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " and umm, vintage handkerchiefs y&#146;know &#145;cause, people cry at weddings.  i&#146;m just gonna grab a couple of these.", "answer": " this stuff is great!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " oh, i forgot this was in here. umm, this was the uh garter that i was saving for my wedding and i wanted it to be monica&#146;s something borrowed and it&#146;s blue.  yeah&#133;", "answer": " y&#146;know rach, i think that, i think you should be monica&#146;s made of honor.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " you do? why?", "answer": " because i think it means more to you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " but pheebs, y&#146;know you earned it.", "answer": " its fine. i mean, this is something that you&#146;ve been thinking about since you were what, 14?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " no, i was ten. i just developed early.", "answer": "  man alive!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": "  hey, what&#146;s going on?", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " well, we just decided that rachel is gonna be your maid of honor.", "answer": "  ohh, wow! that&#146;s great!  oh wow! we really have to start planning! i have, i have a lot of really specific ideas! we should probably get together like four times per week. you can come over to my place; we&#146;ll get together before work! what do you say, 6:30, my place? i&#146;m so excited!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " great nap.", "answer": " it really was.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep6.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}]